Guide to the William Saroyan Papers, 1926-1981
Department of Special Collections
- Manuscripts, 1928-1981., Series 5
  - Novels, Subseries 5.01
    - The Dirty Torch: Original TS, chapters 1-26,1950 (Carton 36, Folder 2)
    - The Dirty Torch: Original TS, chapters 27-41,1950 (Carton 36, Folder 3)
    - The Dirty Torch: TS carbon,1950 (Carton 36, Folder 4)
    - The Dirty Torch: Misc,n.d. (Carton 36, Folder 5)
    - The Early Life of an Ordinary Man: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 36, Folder 6)
    - Epi and Cam: TS,1969 (Carton 36, Folder 7)
    - Epi and Cam: TS copy, annotated,1969 (Carton 36, Folder 8)
    - Epi and Cam: TS copy, annotated,1969 (Carton 36, Folder 9)
    - Epi and Cam: Mimeo TS,1971 (Carton 36, Folder 10)
    - Fifty-Fifty (novel): Film outline,1949 (Carton 36, Folder 11)
    - Fifty-Fifty (novel): TS, corrected,1949 (Carton 36, Folder 12)
    - Fifty-Fifty (novel): Notes,1949 (Carton 36, Folder 13)
    - Fifty-Fifty (novel): TS carbon, corrected,1949 (Carton 36, Folder 14)
    - Fifty-Fifty (novel): TS carbon, corrected,1949 (Carton 36, Folder 15)
    - The Human Comedy: TS orig. screenplay, corrected, in box,1941 (Carton 37, Folder 1)
    - The Human Comedy: TS, with production notes, in box,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 2)
    - The Human Comedy: TS, corrected,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 3)
    - The Human Comedy: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 37, Folder 4)
    - The Human Comedy: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 37, Folder 5)
    - The Human Comedy: Setting copy,n.d. (Carton 37, Folder 6)
    - The Human Comedy: Galleys,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 7)
    - The Human Comedy: Misc. page proofs,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 8)
    - The Human Comedy: Galleys,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 9)
    - The Human Comedy: Galleys,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 10)
    - The Human Comedy: Page proofs, pp. 9-204, corrected,1943 (Carton 37, Folder 11)
    - The Human Comedy: Page proofs, pp. 205-306, corrected,1943 (Carton 37, Folder 12)
    - The Human Comedy: Notes,n.d. (Carton 37, Folder 13)
    - The Human Comedy: Movie production notes,1942 (Carton 37, Folder 14)
    - The Human Comedy: TS carbon; tearsheet,1964 (Carton 37, Folder 15)
    - The Human Comedy: Galleys; introductions for revised edition,1966 (Carton 37, Folder 16)
    - The Human Comedy: Misc.,1976 (Carton 37, Folder 17)
    - The Human Comedy: Published in Omnibook, in French,1948 (Carton 37, Folder 18)
    - The Human Comedy: Dutch version,1962 (Carton 37, Folder 19)
    - The Laughing Matter: TS, corrected, chap. 1-20,1950(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 1)
    - The Laughing Matter: TS, chapters 21-42,1950(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 2)
    - The Laughing Matter: TS carbon, corrected,1951(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 3)
    - The Laughing Matter: TS carbon,1950(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 4)
    - The Laughing Matter: Galleys, corrected,1952(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 5)
    - The Laughing Matter: Galleys, corrected,1952(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 6)
    - The Laughing Matter: Galleys, corrected,1952(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 7)
    - The Laughing Matter: Galleys,1952(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 8)
    - The Laughing Matter: Misc. front matter,1953(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 9)
    - The Laughing Matter: Jacket; advertising copy,1952(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 10)
    - The Laughing Matter: Misc.,n.d.(see also: A Secret Story) (Carton 38, Folder 11)
    - Mama, I Love You: TS, corrected,1955 (Carton 38, Folder 12)
    - Mama, I Love You: Titled "A Bouncing Ball", TS, annotated,n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 13)
    - Mama, I Love You: Misc.,n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 14)
    - Mama, I Love You: Setting copy. Title changed from "All about a little girl,"n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 15)
    - Mama, I Love You: Titled "I Love You, Mama Girl," galleys,n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 16)
    - Mama, I Love You: Galleys,n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 17)
    - Mama, I Love You: Proof sheets, front matter, flap copy,n.d. (Carton 38, Folder 18)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "The Immigrant's Son," TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 39, Folder 1)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "The Immigrant's Son," TS carbon, annotated,1956 (Carton 39, Folder 2)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "The Way it Turns Out," TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 39, Folder 3)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "Old Nose," TS carbon, corrected,1957 (Carton 39, Folder 4)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "The California Poppy Field," TS,1962 (Carton 39, Folder 5)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: TS,1962 (Carton 39, Folder 6)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Titled "The California Poppy Field," TS carbon,1963 (Carton 39, Folder 7)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Setting copy,n.d. (Carton 39, Folder 8)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Galleys,n.d. (Carton 39, Folder 9)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Galleys, marked set,1964 (Carton 39, Folder 10)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Galleys,1964 (Carton 39, Folder 11)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Jacket copy,1964 (Carton 39, Folder 12)
    - One Day in the Afternoon of the World: Annotated envelope,1964 (Carton 39, Folder 13)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Boy and A Man," TS, corrected,1953 (Carton 40, Folder 1)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Boy and A Man," TS,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 2)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Boy and A Man," TS, corrected, chap. 5-11,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 3)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Boy and A Man," mimeo, corrected,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 4)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Notes,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 5)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "My Father is a Writer," mimeo, corrected,1954 (Carton 40, Folder 8)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "Man and Boy, or My Father's Cookbook, or My Father is a Writer," title page, annotated,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 9)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Father and a Son," TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 10)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "A Father and a Son," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 11)
    - Papa You're Crazy: TS carbon, corrected,1956 (Carton 40, Folder 12)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Tearsheet,1956 (Carton 40, Folder 13)
    - Papa You're Crazy: TS carbon, setting copy,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 14)
    - Papa You're Crazy: TS carbon,1951 (Carton 40, Folder 15)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Original illustrations,n.d. (Carton 40, Folder 16)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Front matter,1957 (Carton 40, Folder 17)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Galleys, n.d.(see also oversized) (Carton 40, Folder 18)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Page proofs,1957 (Carton 40, Folder 19)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Page proofs,1958 (Carton 40, Folder 20)
    - Papa You're Crazy: Titled "My Father is a Writer," mimeo,1954 (Carton 40, Folder 67)
    - Pointy Shoes: TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 41, Folder 1)
    - Pointy Shoes: TS, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 41, Folder 2)
    - Pointy Shoes: Misc. notes,1956 (Carton 41, Folder 3)
    - Pointy Shoes: Tearsheet,1965 (Carton 41, Folder 4)
    - Rock Wagram: TS orig., corrected, in box,1950 (Carton 41, Folder 5)
    - Rock Wagram: TS, corrected, pp. 1-197,1950 (Carton 41, Folder 6)
    - Rock Wagram: TS carbon, corrected, pp. 198-357,1950 (Carton 41, Folder 7)
    - Rock Wagram: TS carbon, pp. 1-170,1950 (Carton 41, Folder 8)
    - Rock Wagram: TS carbon, corrected, pp. 171-354,1950 (Carton 41, Folder 9)
    - Rock Wagram: TS, corrected,1951 (Carton 41, Folder 10)
    - Rock Wagram: Galleys,1951 (Carton 41, Folder 11)
    - Rock Wagram: Galleys,n.d. (Carton 41, Folder 12)
    - Rock Wagram: Proofs, mock-ups,1951 (Carton 41, Folder 13)
    - Rock Wagram: Publicity,1951 (Carton 41, Folder 14)
    - Rock Wagram: Misc.,n.d. (Carton 41, Folder 15)
    - A Secret Story: Galleys, 2 sets,n.d.(see also: The Laughing Matter) (Carton 41, Folder 16)
    - A Torch for Life: TS carbon, corrected,1949 (Carton 41, Folder 17)
    - A Torch for Life: TS carbon, corrected,1949 (Carton 41, Folder 18)
    - Tra: A Novel: TS, corrected,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 19)
    - Tra: A Novel: Mimeo, edited,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 20)
    - Tra: A Novel: Mimeo, corrected,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 21)
    - Tra: A Novel: TS photocopy,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 22)
    - Tra: A Novel: Notes,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 23)
    - Tra: A Novel: Misc.,1974 (Carton 41, Folder 24)
    - Tra La: Another Novel: TS, corrected,1974 (Carton 42, Folder 1)
    - Tra La: Another Novel: Mimeo,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 2)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 42, Folder 3)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS, setting copy, corrected,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 4)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS carbon, corrected,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 5)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS carbon, corrected,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 6)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS, 1st ms.,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 7)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS carbon, 2nd ms, corrected,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 8)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Setting copy, 3rd ms.,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 9)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Revisions,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 10)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Galleys, TS,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 11)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Galleys, edited,1951 (Carton 42, Folder 12)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Galleys, annotated, 2 sets,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 13)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Page proofs,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 14)
    - Tracy's Tiger: Page proofs, mock-ups,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 15)
    - Tracy's Tiger: TS carbon, arranged for concert reading by B.G. Hulsopple,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 16)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: "The Adventures of William Saroyan," TS, corrected,1944 (Carton 42, Folder 17)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: "The Adventures of William Saroyan," TS carbon, corrected, annotated,1946 (Carton 42, Folder 18)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: "The Adventures of William Saroyan," titled "I Write...," TS carbon,1946 (Carton 42, Folder 19)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: "The Adventures of William Saroyan," galleys,n.d. (Carton 42, Folder 20)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: "The Adventures of William Saroyan," galleys,1946 (Carton 42, Folder 21)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: Titled "Two Adventures," notes,1949 (Carton 42, Folder 22)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: Notes,1949 (Carton 42, Folder 23)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: Jacket copy,1944 (Carton 42, Folder 24)
    - The Twin Adventures: The Adventures of William Saroyan, a Diary; The Adventures of Wesley Jackson, a Novel: TS carbon, unpublished material,1944 (Carton 42, Folder 25)
  - Plays, Subseries 5.02
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: 2 stage drawings by K. Koga,n.d. (Oversize 1)
    - Abe Lincoln in Lincoln Center: Mimeo TS,1979 (Carton 43, Folder 1)
    - The Abracadabra Kid: TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 43, Folder 2)
    - The Abracadabra Kid: TS, corrected, 2 copies,1952 (Carton 43, Folder 3)
    - The Abracadabra Kid: TS carbons, 2 copies,1953 (Carton 43, Folder 4)
    - The Abracadabra Kid: "First Revised",1953 (Carton 43, Folder 5)
    - The Abracadabra Kid: Mimeo TS,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 6)
    - The Accident: TS, corrected,1958 (Carton 43, Folder 7)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Original TS, corrected,1940 (Carton 43, Folder 8)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,1940 (Carton 43, Folder 9)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 10)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Introduction,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 11)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Proofs,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 12)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning: Misc. program notes; memorabilia,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 13)
    - Afton Water: TS, corrected,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 14)
    - Afton Water: TS, corrected,1942 (Carton 43, Folder 15)
    - Afton Water: TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 16)
    - Afton Water: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 17)
    - Afton Water: Notes,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 18)
    - Afton Water: Notes,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 19)
    - Afton Water: Misc.,1943 (Carton 43, Folder 20)
    - Again the Time of Your Life: TS, corrected,1960 (Carton 43, Folder 21)
    - Ah, Blooming Universe: TS,1956 (Carton 43, Folder 22)
    - Ah Sweet Mystery of Mrs. Murphy: TS, corrected,1958 (Carton 43, Folder 23)
    - Ah Sweet Mystery of Mrs. Murphy: TS carbon, corrected,1958 (Carton 43, Folder 24)
    - Ah Sweet Mystery of Mrs. Murphy: Omnibus scripts, 2 copies, corrected and annotated,1959 (Carton 43, Folder 25)
    - Ah Sweet Mystery of Mrs. Murphy: Omnibus script mimeo,1959 (Carton 43, Folder 26)
    - All Us Jackasses Lifting Our Glasses: TS,1975 (Carton 43, Folder 27)
    - America: TS, 2 copies,1974 (Carton 43, Folder 28)
    - The Annual Meeting of the Mother Church: TS, corrected,1971 (Carton 43, Folder 29)
    - The Annual Meeting of the Mother Church: Mimeo,1971 (Carton 43, Folder 30)
    - Antranik in California: TS,1973 (Carton 43, Folder 31)
    - Anybody and Anybody Else: TS, corrected,1967 (Carton 43, Folder 32)
    - Anybody and Anybody Else: TS; cover,1967 (Carton 43, Folder 33)
    - Anything Anybody Anywhere Anytime Anyhow: TS; copy,1974 (Carton 43, Folder 34)
    - Arena and Referee: TS, 2 copies,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 35)
    - Arena, Ring and Referee: TS,1971 (Carton 43, Folder 36)
    - Arena, Ring and Referee: Mimeo TS,1971 (Carton 43, Folder 37)
    - Armenia Abandoned, Turkey Triumphant, or Something: TS,1974 (Carton 43, Folder 38)
    - The Armenian Play: TS,1973 (Carton 43, Folder 39)
    - Armenians: TS,1971 (Carton 43, Folder 40)
    - Armenians: Mimeo script, corrected and annotated,1973 (Carton 43, Folder 41)
    - Armenians: News release; program note,1974 (Carton 43, Folder 42)
    - The Armenians: TS,1941 (Carton 43, Folder 43)
    - Armenians and Armenians or The Saroyans: TS,1972 (Carton 43, Folder 44)
    - The Babylonian Confusion: TS, corrected,1956 (Carton 43, Folder 45)
    - The Babylonian Confusion: TS carbon, corrected,1956 (Carton 43, Folder 46)
    - The Babylonian Confusion: TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 47)
    - The Bad Men: TS, corrected,1950 (Carton 43, Folder 48)
    - The Bad Men: TS, corrected; from the series "The Wonderful World of W. Saroyan,1952 (Carton 43, Folder 49)
    - The Bad Men: Omnibus scripts,1952 (Carton 43, Folder 50)
    - The Bad Men: Introduction,1952 (Carton 43, Folder 51)
    - The Bad Men: Omnibus script, "Original copy",1952 (Carton 43, Folder 52)
    - The Bad Men: TS, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 53)
    - Bad Men in the West: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 43, Folder 54)
    - Bang! Bang! You're Dead!: TS, 2 copies,1940 (Carton 43, Folder 55)
    - The Beautiful People: TS, corrected,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 1)
    - The Beautiful People: TS, revised,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 2)
    - The Beautiful People: TS, corrected,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 3)
    - The Beautiful People: TS carbons, annotated and corrected, 4 copies,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 4)
    - The Beautiful People: TS carbon,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 5)
    - The Beautiful People: Notes,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 6)
    - The Beautiful People: Notes; misc.,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 7)
    - The Beautiful People: Titled "The Beautiful People and Two Other Plays," TS,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 8)
    - The Beautiful People: Notes; postcards re the production,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 9)
    - The Beautiful People: Stage manager's statistics,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 10)
    - The Beautiful People: Financial statements,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 11)
    - The Beautiful People: Audit - The Beautiful People Co.,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 12)
    - The Beautiful People: Advertising schedule,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 13)
    - The Beautiful People: Misc.,1941 (Carton 44, Folder 14)
    - The Beginning of a New Nation: A Ballet - Play: TS, corrected, 2 copies,1950 (Carton 44, Folder 15)
    - The Best Year in the History of the Whole World: TS, corrected, 2 copies,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 16)
    - The Best Year in the History of the Whole World: Mimeo scripts, 3 copies,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 17)
    - The Best Year in the History of the Whole World: Misc.,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 18)
    - Bicentennial Sleep: TS carbons, 2 copies; photocopies,1974 (Carton 44, Folder 19)
    - Bitlis Forever and Never: TS,1975 (Carton 44, Folder 20)
    - A Bouncing Ball: TS,1950 (Carton 44, Folder 21)
    - The British Bullfighter and the Spanish Pianist: TS,1973 (Carton 44, Folder 22)
    - Broadway and Forget It: Titled "Broadway," TS, annotated,1970 (Carton 44, Folder 23)
    - Broadway and Forget It: TS copy; mimeo,1971 (Carton 44, Folder 24)
    - The Bulgarian Rhapsody: TS,1979 (Carton 44, Folder 25)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Titled "A California Boyhood," TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 44, Folder 26)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Omnibus script,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 27)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Omnibus scripts,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 28)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Omnibus script, corrected,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 29)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Titled "Scenes from the California Boyhood of William Saroyan," Omnibus script carbon,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 30)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Notes; drafts,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 31)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Cast list; notes,n.d. (Carton 44, Folder 32)
    - The California Boyhood of William Saroyan: Contracts,1955 (Carton 44, Folder 33)
    - Cash, a Very Clean Dirty Play: TS, corrected,1969 (Carton 44, Folder 34)
    - Cash, a Very Clean Dirty Play: Mimeo,1971 (Carton 44, Folder 35)
    - Cash, a Very Clean Dirty Play: Annotated title pages,1971 (Carton 44, Folder 36)
    - Cat and Dog: TS,1970 (Carton 44, Folder 37)
    - Cat and Dog: Mimeo,1971 (Carton 44, Folder 38)
    - Cat, Mouse, Man, Woman: TS, corrected,1957 (Carton 44, Folder 39)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS,1955 (Carton 45, Folder 1)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Added material; rewrites,1955 (Carton 45, Folder 2)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Mimeo,1956 (Carton 45, Folder 3)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS, corrected,1955 (Carton 45, Folder 4)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS carbon,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 5)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS, corrected,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 6)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Mimeo,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 7)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Script,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 8)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Mimeo script, edited,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 9)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS carbon,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 10)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Mimeo script,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 11)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS carbon, setting copy,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 12)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS; mimeo,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 13)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS; mimeo,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 14)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 15)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS, corrected, 2 copies,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 16)
    - The Cave Dwellers: TS, revised,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 17)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Revisions; misc. pages,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 18)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Songs,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 19)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Playbill,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 20)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Tearsheets; TS, corrected,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 21)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Misc. jacket copy; TS,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 22)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Introductory material for G.P. Putnam edition,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 23)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Reviews for publishing; setting copy,1957 (Carton 45, Folder 24)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Galleys, Putnam,1958 (Carton 45, Folder 25)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Galleys, G.P. Putnam,1958 (Carton 45, Folder 26)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Page proofs, Faber & Faber,1958 (Carton 45, Folder 27)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Press clippings sheet,n.d. (Carton 45, Folder 28)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Program, West Texas State Univ.,1968 (Carton 45, Folder 29)
    - The Cave Dwellers: Polish translation,1960 (Carton 45, Folder 30)
    - Child, Childbirth, Childhood, Children: TS, corrected,1962 (Carton 46, Folder 1)
    - Child, Childbirth, Childhood, Children: TS carbons, corrected, 2 copies,1967 (Carton 46, Folder 2)
    - Child, Childbirth, Childhood, Children: Titled "Time and Time Again," misc.,1962 (Carton 46, Folder 3)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: Titled "The Year End Play," TS, corrected, 2 copies,1953 (Carton 46, Folder 4)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: Titled "Chris on Christmas Day," TS carbon, corrected,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 5)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: Titled "Chris on Christmas Day," TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 6)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: TS, corrected,1953 (Carton 46, Folder 7)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: TS, 2 copies, corr. (Carton 46, Folder 8)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: Misc.,1953 (Carton 46, Folder 9)
    - Chris Sick, or Happy New Year Anyway: Galleys, 2 sets,1969 (Carton 46, Folder 10)
    - The Christmas Tie: TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 46, Folder 11)
    - The Christmas Tie: Omnibus TS, corrected,1952 (Carton 46, Folder 12)
    - The Christmas Tie: Omnibus script, "original copy",n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 13)
    - The Christmas Tie: TS carbon,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 14)
    - The Christmas Tie: Fragment,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 15)
    - The Christmas Tie: ANTA album mimeo,1955 (Carton 46, Folder 16)
    - The Churchbell Prize Winners: TS,1975 (Carton 46, Folder 17)
    - Coming Through the Rye: TS, corrected; TS carbon, corrected,1939 (Carton 46, Folder 18)
    - The Creative Writing Course: TS,1974 (Carton 46, Folder 19)
    - A Daughter to Think About or A Look at the People: TS,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 20)
    - The Dead: 1-week Play: TS,1974 (Carton 46, Folder 21)
    - The Death of Leo Tallstone: TS, corrected,1961 (Carton 46, Folder 22)
    - The Death of Leo Tallstone: TS carbon,1967 (Carton 46, Folder 23)
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: TS, corrected,1942 (Carton 46, Folder 24)
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: TS, corrected,1943 (Carton 46, Folder 25)
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: TS carbon, corrected,1943 (Carton 46, Folder 26)
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: TS carbon, corrected,1947 (Carton 46, Folder 27)
    - A Decent Birth, A Happy Funeral: TS, corrected,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 28)
    - Dirge for the Dirty Dog Who Stole Sam Cooke's Tennessee Williams' Waltz Girl: TS; copy,1974 (Carton 46, Folder 29)
    - DJANGO, or Fun Around the World: TS,1960 (Carton 46, Folder 30)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: Titled "Lily Dafon," Zanuck Productions script, annotated,1959 (Carton 46, Folder 31)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: Titled "Lily Dafon," Zanuck script, corrected,1959 (Carton 46, Folder 32)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: Zanuck Productions script,1959 (Carton 46, Folder 33)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: Mimeo,1968 (Carton 46, Folder 34)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: William Morris Agency mimeo,1968 (Carton 46, Folder 35)
    - The Dogs, or The Paris Comedy: Galleys, 2 sets,n.d. (Carton 46, Folder 36)